[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 2
The Echo Demon Strikes]
Master, are you alright?
Why doesn't it work
even when he cuts out his own heart?
Don't kill him.
Look.
Master, his spiritual power--
it's flowing toward your heart.
He cuts his heart,
and I suffer.
It seems that
although this half of my heart has been
parted from me for a century,
we were once one.
The bond remains.
If anything happens to him,
this half within me
would likely be shattered.
Unless
he cuts out his heart willingly.
I'm not dead.
What happened?
You're awake.
Who are you?
Chen Xiaohu,
the one and only constable
in Yin-Yang Crossing.
Constable?
Well, in Yin-Yang Crossing,
public order is exceptionally good now,
so there's really nothing
for a constable like me to do.
My daily duties mainly involve
compiling the county records,
and painting portraits for Lady Fufeng,
which is also a major part
of my daily work.
As for you,
you barely arrived
and got thrown in here by Lady Fufeng.
How did you offend her?
I am Bai Shanjun,
the newly appointed county magistrate.
So you are the magistrate.
There hasn't been a magistrate
in Yin-Yang Crossing for years.
Did you offend someone at court?
Why were you exiled to this place?
Is this the county yamen?
This is Xiqian.
This is Xiqianhua.
Xiqianhua?
Why is the county yamen located
inside Xiqianhua?
Come on.
Bro.
Didn't you ask your predecessors
before coming here?
There has been no law
in Yin-Yang Crossing for a long time,
let alone a county yamen.
We
all work for Lady Fufeng.
Lady Fufeng is the eternal master
of Yin-Yang Crossing.
I know.
I came here
just to idle my days away.
I didn't expect
to offend someone right after arriving.
Now they want me dead.
Had I known taking this post
would cost me my life,
I would have resigned
and headed home to rest.
Whatever you think,
take my advice:
This isn't a place you or I can control,
even if we wanted to.
Beneath your feet lies a borderland
where the living, the dead,
and spirits,
along with countless unknown things,
all live together.
What borderland?
All I see is a bunch of charlatans
playing ghosts,
and a flock of gullible fools
who can be manipulated at will.
I know.
Every place has its own ecosystem.
I have no intention
of disrupting it rashly.
Once my time is up
and my term ends,
I will leave here.
It's only been six months
since I passed the imperial exams.
I'm not wasting my life
in this cursed place.
It can't even be wiped clean.
Master, I find this man very strange.
What's strange?
He clearly bears half your heart
within him,
yet seems completely unaware of its power.
He possesses earth-shattering power,
but speaks like the most stubborn mortal.
Most importantly,
he looks so much like...
Why is it so dirty?
You sure have adapted quickly.
Take things as they come.
It's quite nice to be this carefree.
My salary keeps rolling in anyway.
Now you're getting it, bro!
Let me tell you,
that's the right attitude.
Even if the sky falls,
Lady Fufeng will be there to hold it up.
Otherwise,
just that echo demon recently
would be enough to give you a hard time.
Echo demon?
Echo demon.
Did you really hear
Lady Fufeng's statue speak?
Probably just the wind blowing the wood.
You must be hard of hearing
to have missed it.
I heard it clearly from my room
after midnight.
Isn't that normal?
Nonsense.
Why does it smell so bad?
What is that smell?
Did the offerings go bad?
The smell is coming from under the table.
Someone's dead!
I'll strangle you.
Scream again, and I'll strangle you.
Who's talking?
Who... Who's talking?
Wait for me.
Don't go so fast!
W-what is that noise?
Someone is beating the willow drum.
Five strikes of the drum
means that a murder has occurred.
A murder?
Whatever case it is,
it has nothing to do with us.
Lady Fufeng will handle it.
Greetings, Lady Fufeng.
Bootlicker.
You two,
come with me.
[Fufeng's Mansion]
Lady Fufeng.
No evil power.
No demonic aura either.
Master,
the identity of the corpse
has been confirmed.
It's Widow Liu from Shi Village.
Looking at the corpse,
there are bruises on the neck.
It was done by a mortal.
Why don't you take a look
and figure out what happened?
Me?
I... I don't think that's necessary.
It's better left to Lady Fufeng...
I forgot to introduce him to everyone.
This is our new county magistrate
of Yin-Yang Crossing.
Bai Shanjun.
Lord Bai.
He is the new magistrate.
The new magistrate.
Lord Bai.
We haven't had a magistrate here
for a long time.
You are the head of this county.
You should take a look.
Just as that lady said earlier,
the victim was strangled from behind,
which caused her death.
This is a mortal murder case.
Are you sure this is a mortal murder
and not the work of evil demons?
The cause is unclear,
so I dare not jump to conclusions.
But I believe there are no demons
in this world,
only people causing mischief
in their guise.
How can this magistrate be so ignorant?
The cause is unclear,
so I dare not jump to conclusions.
But I believe there are no demons
in this world,
only people causing mischief
in their guise.
Who is mimicking me?
Causing mischief in their guise.
I'll strangle you.
Scream again, and I'll strangle you.
My Lord... My...
This... This is the echo demon.
Scream again, and I'll strangle you.
Echo demon.
Don't panic, everyone!
I haven't finished my painting yet.
Lady Fufeng is here with us.
What's there to panic about?
With Lady Fufeng here,
what is there to fear?
Right, right.
I am a bit tired today.
Since Magistrate Bai is here,
let's leave the investigation to him.
This...
Lady Fufeng,
absolutely not!
Please, Lady Fufeng, take charge!
Yes.
Yes, My Lady.
This echo demon is committing crimes,
and we outsiders can’t handle it.
Please...
Please use Xiqianhua.
Lady Fufeng,
the people are terrified.
They all believe this is demon work.
Following the usual practice,
it's best left to you to handle.
Exactly.
Lady Fufeng,
the people trust you.
You should give them an explanation
to put their minds at ease.
I just arrived at Yin-Yang Crossing.
I'm still unfamiliar with the ropes.
Yin-Yang Crossing has its own laws
and rules.
Having me investigate the case
would be nothing but a waste of time.
Lord Bai,
you sure know how to adapt to situations.
Yin-Yang Crossing can be special,
but it cannot be lawless.
If the case is yours,
there's no escaping it.
How about we make a bet?
I won't touch this corpse.
You can search the ancestral hall
as you please.
The village is under your control.
Everything is up to you.
If you find the real culprit,
I will personally
write a recommendation letter
to send you back to the capital.
But
if within three days,
you fail to find the real culprit,
whether they be mortal or demon.
Then
you shall end your own life on the spot,
and cut out your heart for me.
How about that?
My Lady.
Are you asking me to investigate the case,
or do you simply want me dead?
I just want to see
what you will do.
What can I do?
I studied so hard
to pass the imperial exams,
only to be assigned
to an incompetent noble's son.
I had to take the blame for everything.
With no way to appeal,
his father plotted against me
and had me dispatched to this
godforsaken, monstrous place!
Fine. I accept it.
You rule this place.
I never wanted to overstep my bounds.
But you tried to kill me time and again.
Kill me if you want,
but forcing me to take my own life?
Do you even have to decide
how I should die?
Lord Bai,
calm yourself.
This bet is not
a bad deal for you.
My recommendation letter
carries weight with your emperor.
Do I have a choice?
Fine. I accept.
The victim has distinct
four-finger bruises on the throat.
Her hyoid bone is dislocated.
There is internal bleeding and fluid
in the chest cavity.
The joints are stiff.
There are overlapping scratches
on the back of the hand
with blood and dirt
under the fingernails.
But why are there oil stains on the wound?
Help!
In short,
the victim struggled violently
before her death.
It was not an accidental death,
nor was it caused by demons.
Instead, she was strangled to death
by human hands.
The priority is to find the real culprit
as soon as possible.
Strangled to death?
But we clearly heard
the statue talking yesterday.
Yeah.
My Lord.
Exactly. I heard it just now too.
Didn't you hear it just now?
That ''strangle you'' part.
Right.
Wasn't Widow Liu strangled to death?
Stop!
How dare you smash Lady Fufeng's statue!
Do you want to die?
Wh-wha-?
What is going on here?
This...
Come for me.
Leave it alone.
Hold court!
What's your name?
Where do you live?
The villagers call me Shuan.
My parents passed away.
I've been living in the ruined temple
outside the village.
Ruined temple! Ruined temple!
While at the ancestral hall,
did you see any strange people
or anything unusual?
I don't know.
I was starving so badly,
so I taught the parrot
to mimic human speech
to fake a demon just to get some food.
I didn't mean to really scare anyone.
You still shouldn't do that.
Are you the village chief?
No.
The village chief isn't here,
so I'm acting on his behalf.
I am Shi Quan,
the deputy magistrate
of Yin-Yang Crossing.
Last night,
did any of you hear what this parrot said?
I did.
It said, "Don't scream. Don't scream."
''Scream again, and I'll strangle you.''
Don't scream! Don't scream!
Scream again, and I'll strangle you.
That's Village Chief Zhou's voice.
I've long heard
that the village chief has had his eye
on Widow Liu for a long time.
No wonder.
Village Chief Zhou hasn't been seen
for three days.
Deputy Magistrate Shi,
start a search immediately.
Yes.
My Lord,
I'm a civil official.
Aren't you a constable?
I...
I haven't arrested anyone in a long time.
Arrest! Arrest!
Whispers echo in the forest,
each cry like weeping.
Mimicking human speech,
it drains away vitality.
Old things return,
shifting within the heart.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
Shuan.
Did you ever teach this parrot
to sing nursery rhymes?
I taught it to mimic human speech,
but not any nursery rhymes.
Nursery rhymes?
The children have been chanting it lately.
At the wine merchant's murder scene,
someone also heard it.
Lady Fufeng,
The money in the house
of Village Chief Zhou Ming
has long been gone.
I'm afraid he has already absconded.
Zhou Ming must be arrested immediately.
This case cannot be looked at
in isolation.
The wine merchant's sudden death
and Widow Liu's case in the ancestral hall
both connect to the rumor of echo demon
and the eerie nursery rhyme.
These two cases
should be investigated together.
You aim quite high, Lord Bai.
With only three days
and so much on your plate,
be careful you cannot wrap things up.
My Lady.
Whether I can wrap things up,
is that up to me?
You want me dead,
but I want to live.
As you wish.
However,
I also have a request.
It comes with me.
Following you,
who knows what kind of trouble
it will cause.
My Lady.
It is important physical evidence
and should be kept in my custody.
Fine then.
The bird's gone.
It seems
Lord Bai is not very lucky.
Now you've lost your last bargaining chip.
You'd better just look
for Village Chief Zhou.
There's not much time left.
Revealing your demon form
and disrupting the order
of the human world,
have you forgotten the rules of Xiqianhua?
Forgive me, My Lady.
It's not that I forgot,
but that child,
Shuan, he was good to me.
I wanted to get him some food.
The day I hid in the statue,
I heard something.
V-Village Chief Zhou.
Good lady,
you must be lonely all by yourself.
Why don't you just give in to me?
Don't move.
Come here.
Help! Help!
Don't scream! Don't scream!
Help!
Scream again, and I'll strangle you.
I didn't want to reveal myself
and cause panic,
so I mimicked his voice,
the village chief's voice
to scare them,
so that the corpse would be found sooner.
The wine merchant's case a few days ago,
was it related to you?
No... no.
It wasn't.
Shuan and I have never left the village.
I just heard that nursery rhyme around.
I... I really haven't harmed anyone.
Alright, go rest now.
Whispers echo in the forest,
each cry like weeping.
Mimicking human speech,
it drains away vitality.
Old things return,
shifting within the heart.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.